现在，让我们尝试使用迭代器来完成一个简单的工作。
Now, let's try using our iterator for a simple job.
假设我们有一份麻省理工学院的课程表
Suppose we have a list of MIT subjects represented
作为字符串，比如6005803900。
as strings, like 6005, 803, 900.
我们想要一个方法删除课程6，删除课程6
We want a method drop course 6 that will delete the course 6
列表中的主题，比如这个，
subjects from the list, like this one,
但把其他的话题抛在脑后。
but leave the other subjects behind.
现在，遵循好的实践，我们首先编写规范。
Now, following good practices, we first write the spec.
请注意，本规范在其合同中有一个条款
Notice that this spec has a clause in its contract
这会警告客户机其列表参数将发生变化。
that warns the client that its list argument will be mutated.
然后按照测试优先编程，
Then following test first programming,
我们设计了一个测试策略
we devise a testing strategy that
划分输入空间。
partitions the input space.
然后我们选择测试用例来覆盖这个分区。
And then we choose test cases to cover that partition.
最后，我们实现了它。
And then finally, we implement it.
所以我们使用迭代器
And so we're using the iterator that we've just
创建以迭代主题数组列表
created to iterate over the array list of subjects
我们得到的。
that we've been given.
对于每个元素，我们检查该元素是否
And for each element, we check whether that element
从6点开始。
starts with 6 dot.
如果是的话，我们就把它移走
And if it does, then we remove it
从基础集合。
from the underlying collection.
现在我们运行测试用例。
Now we run our test cases.
注意我们写的是为了让他们工作，对吧？
And notice we wrote them so that they ought to work, right?
他们要么把名单单独留下
They are either leaving the list alone
或者他们正从6开始删除主题。
or they're removing exactly the subjects that start with 6.
但我们发现最后一次测试
But we discover that this last test
你应该把它们都移走的箱子，失败了。
case, which you're supposed to remove them all, fails.
它留下了一个它应该删除的主题。
It leaves behind a subject that it should have removed.
为什么？
Why?
让我们追查到底发生了什么。
Let's trace through what happens.
使用快照图来显示我的迭代器可能会有帮助
It may help to use a snapshot diagram showing the My Iterator
对象和数组列表对象并更新该关系图
object and the Array List object and update that diagram
当你处理这些代码的时候。
while you work through this code.